There were nine in the bed and Infant Kony said, roll over, roll over. Now everyone is
back in bed, and Infant Kony is saying, welcome back, sports fans. Oh baby, baby, baby, baby, baby...
Beep beep. Beep beep beep beep beep beep beep beep beep beep beep beep. What a weekend. We
had football novices picking Chelsea to beat the Tigers. Clearly haven't had time to
watch any football this season. Former kings of cash, Net Spend FC, took another batch
of players out this week with a snorefest at the Spion Kop library. Isak and Wirtz must
have a super injunction in place, because the media are quiet considering their price tags.
Then there was one Mr Paddle Zest, hadn't put a foot wrong all game, never picked with
the masses, never owned a van, doesn't let anything stop him. One round too far for
Alf, in one of the worst ways to spend 90 minutes: Spurs drew 0-0 and everyone is
back in. If you're listening to this, I hope you've not missed the deadline, because
you know Infant Kony has the wheel ready to spin. Kony, spin me right round, baby, right
round. If I get to know your name, nah nah nah nah, Kony. Well, I could trace your private number, Kony.
All I know is that to me, you look like you're lots of fun, open up your loving
arms. I want some, want some, eye. I set my sights on you and no one else will do, an
eye. I got to have my way now, Kony. All I know is that to me, you look like
you're having fun, open up your loving arms. Watch out, here I come.